Lila Ouadi

Walnut Creek, California 925-948-6320 lilaouadi61@gmail.com

Summary

Conscientious Store Manager with +5 years of experience in directing store operations, leading top-performing sales teams, and providing enjoyable shopping experience to customers. Proven team leader with track record in developing and implementing effective strategies to grow customer base, surpass revenue goals, and exceed sales objectives.

Education

UC Berkley Exentation, Berkeley, California Web Developer

Enrolled - September 2019

Diablo Valley College , Pleasant Hill, California Business

Graduated - May 2019

University Mouloud Mameri, Tizi Ouzou, Tizi Ouzou Province Psychologie HR

Graduated - May 2013

Diablo Valley College , Pleasant Hill, California Associate Teacher ECE

Graduated - December 2018

Employment History

Sunglass Hut, Walnut Creek, California *Store Manager*

April 2017 - Present

- Utilize The Sunglass Hut Experience tools to consistently deliver sales plan and company objectives.
- Develop the store's strategic plan to achieved financial results.
- Lead by example by coaching, developing, mentoring and inspiring the team to enhance store performance.
- People work for people I use this philosophy to grow careers, encourage teamwork and retain talent through a development-focused environment.
- Network, recruit, hire to staffing needs, and trains using the on-boarding tools provided as part of The Sunglass Hut Experience.
- Inspire team growth through individual development plans.
- Create an inspirational and motivating work environment that reflects the integrity of the brand.
- Develop customer relationships through interaction and feedback.

Sunglass Hut, Walnut Creek, California

Sales Supervisor

April 2016 - May 2017

- Utilize The Sunglass Hut Experience tools to consistently deliver sales plan and company objectives.
- Achieve/ex ceed the individual Sales Plan.
- Leverages reporting tools to track individual results and identify wins and areas of opportunity.
- Provide ongoing coaching for all Associates to support growth and development.
- Create an inspirational and motivating work environment that reflects the integrity of the brand.
- Seeks out opportunities for self-development as defined in an individual development plan.
- Act as an ambassador for the Sunglass Hut brands
- Ensure impeccable execution of operational policies and procedures and maintains brand standards.

Whole Foods Market, Walnut Creek, California

Sales Supervisor/ Team trainer

March 2014 - October 2017

- Ex cellent customer service skills and positive attitude
- Handled daily tasks for my departement and make decisions to increase sales, customers
- Generated sales reports, activity reports forecasts and attended all sales meetings and functions
- Developed new customer contacts, doubling customer base since arrival
- Provided leadership to employees in addition to assisting with sales goal development and training
- conduct sales meetings
- Team Member of the year 2016

Professional Skills

Microsoft office

Excel

HTML

Javascript

Excel

Languages

French

Arabic

berber